careerexplorer.com 2019-07-15

# Privacy ‐ CareerExplorer

## Introduction

The Privacy Policy describes CareerExplorer's policies and procedures regarding the personal information and other data collected through the CareerExplorer Site. By using the CareerExplorer Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collection and Use

The CareerExplorer Site is designed to connect individuals to careers and help them find their passion in life. CareerExplorer will store metadata associated with the use of the CareerExplorer Site. 

To better improve our Content and the CareerExplorer Site, we track some of the actions you take on the CareerExplorer Site, such as rating a career or your satisfaction with our product through third-party analytics tools. This information is regularly deleted. 

We use HTTP cookie technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the CareerExplorer Site. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. CareerExplorer may use cookies to better understand how you interact with our Content and improve the CareerExplorer Site. 

CareerExplorer uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide the CareerExplorer Site and to better understand the use of the CareerExplorer Site. These services may collect information sent to your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. 

## Information Protection and Stewardship

The CareerExplorer team takes the protection and stewardship of your information seriously. We take several measures to safeguard your data while it is in our possession. Some of these measures include allowing only traffic only over HTTPS, encrypting our data layers at rest, never storing passwords in plaintext, among many others. 

Further, we firmly believe that you own your data, not us. To that end, when you request an account deletion, we will irreversibly delete all personally identifiable information. It is worth noting that currently **we delete all data associated with your account** , but we reserve the right to maintain anonymized data (such as anonymized responses to our assessment, or anonymized career history) for the purposes of improving our recommendation systems. 

Additionally, in the event of a breach where we believe your information has been compromised, we will inform you within 48 hours, letting you know what has happened, what information we believe to have been exposed, what we have done to remedy the situation, and what steps we believe you should take as a precaution. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

We use the information we collect to make the CareerExplorer Site available to our users, to measure the use of the CareerExplorer Site, to improve the CareerExplorer Site, and to provide you with customer support. We may share or disclose information for these purposes without prior consent. 

We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public posts or the number of users who clicked on a particular piece of Content. 

We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonable necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect CareerExplorer’s rights or property. 

Registered users are encouraged to keep their information current and up to date. The CareerExplorer Site provides users with the tools to access or modify personal information provided to CareerExplorer via the CareerExplorer Site. 

## Third Party Sites and Services

The terms of this Privacy Policy apply only to information that is collected through the CareerExplorer Site. The CareerExplorer Site may contain links to third party sites and/or services, some of which may collect personal data and/or other information from users. CareerExplorer is not in control of or responsible for the privacy practices of those third party sites and/or services. Users are advised to contact the third parties directly for information about their privacy policies. 

## Children

The CareerExplorer Site is intended for users who are at least 13 years of age. Users who are under the age of 13 are not permitted to use the CareerExplorer Site or provide information to the CareerExplorer Site. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

The CareerExplorer Site may change from time to time. As a result, CareerExplorer may need to make changes to this Privacy Policy. 

CareerExplorer reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy without prior notice. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy indicate your agreement with the terms. This Privacy Policy was last updated as of the date indicated above. Please check back and review this Privacy each time before you provide information to the CareerExplorer Site. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the online privacy statement for this site or its implementation you may contact us [here](mailto:contact@sokanu.com).
